<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PORTFOLIO on Thong Nguyen</title>
    <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PORTFOLIO on Thong Nguyen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Thong Nguyen</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Carreer goals</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/carreer-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/carreer-goals/</guid>
      <description>My short-term goals.
Gain a new skill every month that related to my current industry I work for.
Boost my connection to improve my abilities by widening social and professional contacts
Gain experience is my first step. As a freshly graduated student as well as the one who is looking to change fields, an internship may be the best way to get a close look inside my want. But I will try my best to show my bright to get a probation job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cerifications &amp; degrees</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/certifications-degrees/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/certifications-degrees/</guid>
      <description>C Certification
    Java Certification
    Degree of Engineer
    HACKATHON ITSTU
    Social work 2017-2018
    Good student scholarship of learning and forming
    School-level Students of 5 merits Award
    School-level Students of 5 merits Award
    合格証３Q
    合格証３Q score report</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/resume/</guid>
      <description>Nguyễn Quốc Nguyên Thông  Email: quocnguyenthongnguyen@gmail.com
Birthday: 2 Jan
Place: District 8, Ho Chi Minh city
 Objectives: I want to gain technical experience from actual operations, improve my current programming and teamwork skills. I will do my best to get promoted as fast as possible for next 3-4 years. I am now open to learn new technology.
 EDUCATION: SAIGON TECHNOLOGY UNIVERSITY (2015-2019)
Major: Computer Science
GPA: 7.25/10</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sample project</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/</guid>
      <description>In university I made 3 important project.
The fist is using C/C++ built a family free application. This is my first computer project. link to my Family free structures by C programing language
The second one is using PHP to built a e-commerce site. This is my major Web project. Link to my PHP e-commerce site!
And the last one is my graduation project using Spring MVC framework built a e-commerce site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Skills</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/skills/</guid>
      <description>My hard skills that I am confident with:
Typing. I found that a lot of Vietnamese type only with few fingers. It so terrible! Typing with full fingers is the first basic, the first prerequisite. You can not fully concentrate with your task while you look into the screen and look down to see the keyboards
Foreign languages. Nowadays English is a popular language, without English, I think I so hard to survive in competitive environment</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social works</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/social-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/social-works/</guid>
      <description>I often spend my weekend to enjoy social, voluntary activities for community. I also have a lot of achievements like Green Summer Volunteer Campaign, Spring Volunteer Campaign, etc during the last 5 year. Being a dynamic person by connecting people. I think a dynamic person is charismatic and charming. Doing social activities makes my soft skills better, it help me refresh my energy by meeting awesome people and grow me up faster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Work philosophy</title>
      <link>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/work-philosophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 19:47:09 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thongnqnguyen.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/work-philosophy/</guid>
      <description>My philosophy towards work is taking on new challenges, and activities that make you improve and learn on a regular basis, treating others with respect and start with a smile. I’am enjoy speaking with others and I’m very dedicated to helping everyone.
And one more thing, I believe in science, I do not believe in supernatural being.
As a true man I think men should be a little feminine, 100% manly is too coldly.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
